早上好
Morning.
Mornin'.
介意我坐会吗
Mind if I join you?
请自便
Please.
想要吃点鱼吗
Want some fish?
谢谢  我刚吃过
Thank you. I just ate.
我以为你是来这儿是为了那艘船
I take it you're here 'cause of the ship.
是的
I am.
他们怎么找到这岛的
How did they find the island?
等他们到了岛上你再问他们吧
You'll have to ask 'em when they get here.
我不需要问
I don't have to ask.
是你带他们来的
You brought them here.
-仍想证明我错了是吧  -你就是错了
- Still trying to prove me wrong, aren't you? - You are wrong.
我有吗
Am I?
他们来到这里  争斗
They come. They fight.
破坏  腐败
They destroy. they corrupt.
然后是一如既往的结局
It always ends the same.
只会有一次结局
It only ends once.
在那之前的所有事都只是个铺垫
Anything that happens before that is just progress.
你明不明白我多么渴望杀了你吗
Do you have any idea how badly I wanna kill you?
是的
Yes.
迟早的事  总有哪一天
One of these days, sooner or later...
我会找到一个枪眼的  我的朋友
I'm going to find a loophole, my friend.
当你找到时  我会在此静候
Well, when you do, I'll be right here.
和你聊天总是很开心  Jacob
Always nice talking to you, Jacob.
和你聊天我也很开心
Nice talking to you, too.
本字幕由YYeTs人人影视翻译制作
更多字幕 美剧 请登陆 www.YYeTs.net
■
翻译：  冰卡  zhjing  非燕  牛牛  天地义心  兰  夜  大菜
校对：  Afan　　 时间轴： 梁良
■
后期：  冰蚕　　 剧集总监： zhjing，非燕
你要那么做吗
Are you gonna do it?
不  你来吧
Unh-unh. You do it.
- 好吧  我来做  但你来把风可以吧 - 可以
Fine. I'll do it. But you're gonna be lookout, okay? Okay.
今年的收成不错
The crops came in pretty good this year.
你听说了吗  Frank买了那个旧
Hey you hear? Frank bought the old...
是的  我听说他准备开垦那片地
Yeah, I hear he's gonna farm the land
-一直到Ames大道  -我也听说了
- All the way out to Ames road. - Yeah, I hear that, too.
两包烟吗
Two cigarettes?
他会喜欢这些的
There's nothing he would like less.
你们两个小鬼拿了什么
What you kids got there?
打开你的背包
Open your bag.
你哪来的这个
Mm-hmm. Where'd you get this?
-那儿拿的  -我知道你
- Got it over there. - I know you.
-你是Diane Austen的女儿  叫什么  -Katie
- You're Diane Austen's girl. what's your name? - Katie.
Katie  我要打电话给你母亲和警察
Well, Katie, I'm calling your mom, then the cops,
因为我这里不容许偷窃  你明白吗
Because I don't tolerate stealing here. You understand?
没必要那么做
No need to do that.
我来买单
I'll pay for it.
我想这些足够了
I hope this is enough.
只要有人付钱
Well, long as somebody pays for it,
那就没什么大不了的
Guess there's no harm done.
但我不希望再次见到你们没有父母带时
But I don't wanna see you in here ever again
在这里晃悠  懂吗
Without your parents. You understand me?
谢谢你  先生
Thanks, mister.
不客气
You're welcome.
不会再继续偷了  对吧
You're not gonna steal anymore, are you?
乖乖的  Katie
Be good, Katie.
欢迎大家上船
Welcome aboard, everyone.
我们要做一些海上的系统检查
We will be doing some system checks offshore here
然后驶向开阔海域前
Before heading out into the open ocean
再下潜到可控的运行深度
And submerging to our operational running depth.
你们会收到你们的镇静剂
You should be receiving your sedatives,
然后你们会被带到你们的休息仓
And then we will escort you to your sleeping berths.
好好休息  我们到站后再见
Have a nice rest. See you on the other side.
我们得离开这里
We have to get out of here.
离开这里
"out of here"?
我们在水底啊
We're underwater.
你来这里到底干嘛呢
What the hell are you doing here?
你怎么被捉到的呢
How'd you get caught?
-我回来找你的  -找我干嘛
- I came back to get you. - Came back go get me for what?
Jack在哪
Where's Jack
Jack要去引爆一颗氢弹
Jack is on his way to blow up a hydrogen bomb.
他干嘛那么做
Why the hell would he do that?
那有什么影响吗  我们得阻止他
Does it matter? We have to stop him.
对不起  我帮不了你
Sorry, I'm gonna pass.
你听到我说什么了吗
Did you hear what I just said?
我听到你说的了  只是你不明白  Kate
Yeah, I heard you. You just don't get it, Kate.
我们在达摩组织很开心  直到你们出现
We we happy in dharmaville till y'all showed up.
不过这一切都结束了
But now that's all over.
所以我们会喝了这药
So we're gonna drink our O.J.
回到现实社会去碰碰运气
And take our chances in the real world.
Jack想把岛炸飞
Jack wants to blow up the island?
对Jack说是好事
Good for jack.
我们要移动一颗10吨重的炸弹
Is there anything in there about how we're supposed to move
穿越这座岛  有什么看法吗
A 10-ton bomb across the island?
实际上是20吨重
Actually, it's 20 tons.
幸运的是  看起来Faraday没有打算
Fortunately, it seems that Faraday
整个移动这个庞然大物
Never intended to freight the device in its entirety.
什么
What?
他写了详细介绍
He left detailed instructions
来解释如何除去钚核心
On how to remove the Plutonium core...
如何引爆它
And how to detonate it.
Faraday告诉我说我们要消除
Faraday told me that we needed to wipe out
某种能量袋
Some kind of pocket of energy.
只有一部分的炸弹的话足够吗
Is only part of the bomb gonna be enough to do that?
核心部分是一个热核武器 足够了
The core itself is a thermonuclear weapon. It'll be more than enough.
等等
Hey! hey! Wait.
我们20年前把它封起来
We sealed that thing up 20 years ago,
然后我们藏到地下 就因为它会释放核辐射
And we put it underground Because it was emitting radiation.
-这会是个好主意吗  Eloise  -Richard
- Does this sound like a good idea to you, Eloise? - Richard
-你怀孕了  -所以我们才要 帮他们做好这事
- You're pregnant. -Which is exactly why We have to help him see this through
一旦核心移除后
Once the core is removed,
然后怎么办
Then what?
然后我们有大约2个小时
Then we have approximately two hours
-来把它带到天鹅站  -2个小时
- To take it to the swan site. - Two hours?
当Faraday回到岛上的时候
When Faraday returned to the island,
他很清楚这个时间表
He was very explicit about his timetable.
那么  我们最好快点
Well then... we'd better get movin'.
谁要你们停下来不钻的
Who stopped the damn drill?!
我说的
I did.
-为什么  -因为当我们超过70米时
- Why? - Because when we passed 70 meters,
钻头的温度上升到了60度
The drill temp went up 60 degrees,
所以我不希望看到它融化掉
And I didn't want it to melt.
Pierre  所以我们才准备了一卡车水
Well, Pierre, that's why we have a truck full of water.
所以让它冷却  再启动它
So cool it down and turn it on.
Stuart  我们刚把所有无关的人
Stuart, we've just evacuated the island
撤离了这岛
Of all nonessential personnel.
我们可能陷于造反的局面当中
We're in the midst of a possible insurrection.
你真以为现在是个最好的时机
Do you really think this is the ideal time
-来做你的实验吗  -我干这个项目
- For your experiments? - I've been working
有足足六年了
On this project for 6 years.
去设计一个只有在梦想中才能
Designing a station that'll be able
操控电磁场的设备
To manipulate electromagnetism in ways we only dreamed of.
你有没有想过钻入那个孔 会有什么后果吗
Have you thougt about the consequence Of drilling into that pocket?!
我们不知道会
We have no idea what we are going to
如果爱迪生担心试验后果
If Edison was only worried the consequences,
我们现在还处于黑暗中呢
We'd all still be sitting in the dark.
我来这岛上是要改变世界的  Pierre
I came to this island to change the world, Pierre.
我绝对会这么做的
That's exactly what I'm intend to to.
赶紧启动吧
Let's get it started!
三十年后
Thirty years later.
大家休息一下
Take five, everybody.
我们离Jacob住处还有段距离
We still got ways to go to get to Jacob's.
谁是Jacob
Who's Jacob?
他管这个岛
He's in charge of this island.
你曾说是John管
You said John was in charge.
不  我说的是  他是领导着
No, I said he was the leader...
他有这称号的时间可真是短啊
A title that I've discovered is incredibly temporary.
每个人向某人负责
But everyone answers to someone,
领导者向Jacob负责
And the leader answers to Jacob.
他长什么样
What's he like?
我不知道  Sun  我从没见过他
I don't know, Sun. I've never met him.
你盯着我有10分钟了  Richard
You've been staring for the last ten minutes, Richard.
有什么要问我的吗
Is there something you would like to ask me?
Ben说他把你掐死了
Ben told me that... he strangled you.
的确是的
That is my recollection, yes.
他说他确信你死了
He said he was sure you were dead.
他看见你的棺材被抬上
He saw your coffin loaded onto that plane
送你来的那飞机  你怎么还活着
That you came back on. How are you alive?
你在这岛上的时间 比我久得多  Richard
Well, you've been on this island Much longer than I have, Richard.
如果有人能解释这事的话 我想那一定是你
If anyone should have an explanation, I'd think it would be you.
我是一直在这
I-I have been here a long time John.
见过这岛上很多 我无法描述的事情
And i've seen things on this island That I can barely describe.
但我没见过谁能重生
But... i've never seen someone come back to life.
我也没见过谁能不衰老
And i've never seen anyone who doesn't age.
这不意味着这不存在
It doesn't mean it can't happen.
是Jacob使我这样的
I'm this way because of Jacob.
我猜
And if I had to guess,
也是他使你不在棺材里的
He's the reason you're not in that coffin anymore.
我完全同意  Richard
I agree completely, Richard.
这正是我这么做的原因  去感谢他
That's why i'm doing this... so I can thank him.
一旦我做完了  我们就要去
And once I've done that, we're gonna need to deal with
解决那架送我来的飞机上的
The rest of the passengers from the ajira flight
其他乘客
That brought me here.
-"解决"是什么意思  -你知道我什么意思
- What do you mean, "deal with"? - You know what I mean.
走吧
Let's go!
松开那箱子
Untie the crates.
-为什么带上这粗鲁的家伙  -我们可能需要他
- Why'd we even bring this yahoo? - Becae we might need him.
哪里需要  他不知道问题的答案
For what? he didn't know the answer to the question.
那不意味着他不重要
That doesn't mean he's not important.
怎么  你认为他是个候选人吗
What, you think he's a candidate?
他醒着
He's awake.
你偷听多久了
How long you been listening to us?
久到让我在想  我究竟是什么候选人
Long enough to wonder what the hell i'm a candidate for.
-你们到底是什么人  -你朋友
- Who the hell are you people? - We're friends.
你会用步枪打你朋友的脸
So you smack all your friends in the face with a rifle,
并推进船里绑架吗
Shove 'em in a boat and kidnap 'em?
只对我们喜欢的人这么做
Only the ones we like.
盒子里是什么
What's in the box?
听你的
Your call.
打开
Open it.
太棒了
Terrific.
孩子  要笔吗
Need a pen, son?
是的  谢谢
Yeah. thanks.
给你
There you go.
你可以留着它
You can keep it.
对于你父母的死  我感到很遗憾  James
I'm very sorry about your mother and father, James.
Jimmy  走吧  我们要去葬礼了
Come on, Jimmy. We gotta get to the cemetery, okay?
你在写什么
What you writin'?
没什么
Nothin'.
"亲爱的Sawyer先生"
"dear mr. sawyer,
"你不认识我  但我认识你"
"you don't know who I am, but I know who you are,
"我也知道你做了什么"
And I know what you done."
听着  Jimmy
Listen to me, Jimmy.
我知道你对
I know you're angry
导致你爸妈死去的这个人感到很生气
At the man who did this to your mamand daddy.
你有权生气
And hell, you got every right to be.
但你要度过这关  孩子
But you gotta move on, boy.
他们走了
They're gone,
你改变不了的
And there ain't nothin' you can do to change that.
已成定局
What's done is done.
答应我你不要写完这封信
Now promise me you're not gonna finish that letter.
答应你
I promise.
好的
Good.
走吧  去告别
Come on. let's go say good-bye.
我就直说吧
Let me get this straight.
Jack引燃那核武器  一切都变了
Jack sets off a nuke, which somehow resets everything.
815航班没坠毁
So flight 815 never crashes. it just...
而是在洛杉矶平安无事地着陆
Lands in L.A. safe and sound,
这一切都没发生
and none of this ever happen.
Sawyer  如果Jack做了这事
Sawyer, if Jack does this,
他就能杀了岛上的每个人
He could kill everyone on the island.
是的  我听说了
yeah, I heard that part.
-你没意见吗  - 你没听我说  Kate
- And you're okay with that? - You ain't hearing me, Kate.
我做了个选择  现在还在坚持
I made a choice, and I'm sticking to it.
我决定要离开  我就离开
I decided to leave, and I'm leavin'.
这是你的镇静剂
All right, here's your sedatives.
你在干什么
What the hell did you just do?
我们决定离开这岛  James  我们做到了
We decided to leave this island, james. we did.
我们现在要回去
And now we're going back.
-你没开玩笑吧  -我们不能眼看那些人死去
- You serious? - We can't just let those people die.
你走吗
You want out?
还是呆在这里发牢骚
You wanna stay here and whine about it?
解开手铐
Unlock the damn cuffs.
"小蜜蜂"号呼叫总部  系统检查完成
"galaga" to base. the system check is complete.
雷达自动锁定启程方向
We're locked on departure bearing
准备离岛
And ready to leave the island.
收到  "小蜜蜂"号  一路平安
Roger that, "galaga." have a safe trip.
回来时见
See you on the return.
把你的枪给我
Give me your gun.
谢谢  船长
Appreciate that, captain. now
现在请帮助我们
we need you to serve us all.
-什么  我不能让这潜艇  -我想你可以
- What? I can't take this sub… -  oh, I think you can.
我们离开后  继续前进  无论怎样
Once we're gone, proceed on course. whatever you do,
都别把这些人带回岛上  明白吗
Do not take those people back to the island. understand?
如果Horace联系我
And what if Horace tries to contact me?
我该怎么说
What am I supposed to say?
你不在
You ain't home.
走
Go.
-够大了吗  -可以了
- Is this big enough? - That'll do.
Faraday的日志你看了吗  -带上
- Are you done with Faraday's journal? - Take it.
能问个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
20多年前
Over, uh, 20 years ago,
一个叫John Locke的人
A man named John Locke...
走进我们的营地里
He walked right into our camp,
说他将成为我们的领导者
And he told me that he was gonna be our leader.
那以后我离开过这岛三次
Now i've gone off the island three times since then
可我看他没有三头六臂啊
But he never seemed, uh, particularly special to me.
你说你有个问题
You said you had a question.
你认识他吗  这个叫Locke的人
You know him? Locke?
认识
Yeah.
对  我认识他
Yeah, I know him.
我要是你的话  就不会怀疑他的能耐
And if i were you, i wouldn't give up on him.
你为什么没告诉他
Why haven't you told him yet?
告诉谁什么
Told who what?
Richard  你为什么没告诉他我对于Jacob的计划
Richard. why haven't you told him about my plans for Jacob?
John  如果你是指谋杀他的"计划"
If by "plans" you mean murdering him, John,
我想你还是不想声张的
I assume you'd want to keep that a secret.
你怎么没说呢
When did that ever stop you?
自从我女儿威胁我说
Well, I started thinking differently about things
要是我不对你言听计从  就会把我粉身碎骨
When my dead daughter threatened to destroy me
我的思维模式就开始转变了
If i did't do everything you said.
等等  等等
Whoa. w-w-wait. wait.
这是哪里发生的事
Where did this happen?
就在那个神殿底下的洞穴里
In that cavern beneath the temple,
正是我们去找那个怪物的时候
When we went to see the monster.
那就是说
So...
我说什么你都会服从
You're willing to do whatever I say
无论我下的是什么指令
No matter what it is?
没错
Yes.
那好
Well, then...
我就不必非得说服你了
I guess I won't have to convince you after all.
说服我什么
Convince me to do what?
Ben  我不会杀Jacob
I'm not gonna kill Jacob, Ben.
你来动手
You are.
-巴黎还是罗马  -不
- Paris or Rome? - No.
-弗洛伦斯呢  -去哪里都无所谓  Sayid
- Florence? - It doesn't matter, Sayid...
-有所谓  -只要我们在一起就好
- Yes, it does. - As long as we're together.
这可是我们的结婚纪念日  得去最好的地方
It's our anniversary. we have to find the perfect place.
我得找找我的太阳镜
I would settle finding my sun glasses
打扰一下  先生  能帮我个忙吗
Excuse me, sir? Could you you help me?
抱歉  我可能是迷路了  你是洛杉矶来的吗
I'm sorry. I think i'm lost. are you from Los Angeles?
-你要去哪里  -找到啦
- What are you looking for? - I found them.
Nadia
Nadia?
带我回家
Take me home.
没时间了  该走了
Time is short. let's go.
退后
Mm, stand back.
这是达摩组织的居所之一
It's one of the dharma houses.
我打头阵
I'll go first.
Jack  别以为自己大权在握
Jack, don't misunderstand who's in charge here.
我打头阵
I'll go first.
因为如果里面有危险人物
Because if someone at that house is a threat,
你会迟疑  而我不会
You might hesitate... but I won't.
好吧  Eloise  上吧  我们跟在后面
All right. oy, Eloise, go on. after you.
一旦我们给你发出"一切安全"的指令
Once we give you the "alllear,"
你就带上炸弹
Then you bring the bomb.
我们不想发生任何意...
We don't want any acci...oh!
你干什么傻事
What the hell are you doing?
我在保护我们的领导  后退
I'm protecting our leader. get back.
她醒来时一定会气急败坏
She's gonna be angry when she wakes up,
可那也总比她丧命强
But that's a lot better than being dead.
她命令我助你一臂之力  我们帮了你
She ordered me to help you. We helped you.
现在你该靠自己了
Now you're on your own.
我得带她原路返回
And I'm taking her out the way we came in.
你先走
After you.
所有居民注意  现在是黑色警戒
All residents, we are in a code black.
立即带上武器
Report with your weapons
去安保分派处报告
To your security assignments immediately.
如果你们遇到敌人
If you come into contact with a hostile,
可以使用致命武器
You are authorized to use deadly force.
我们该怎么离开这里
How the hell are we gonna get out of here?
快  没时间了
Go! we don't have time!
我们混如人群
We hide in plain sight.
先在兵营周围设置一条警戒线
Set up a perimeter around the barracks first.
你去那边大门守卫  你去带两个
You gonna go over there by the gate. you get two...
你们俩去  你们去塔桥
So you guys go. you go to pylons.
我们去那里集中
We're gathering over there.
你就是那个杀我孩子的杂种
You're the son of a bitch who shot my kid.
别开枪
Don't fire that weapon.
我携带着核装置
I'm carrying a nuclear device.
快走
Hey! let's go!
从太阳的照射角度看
From the looks of the sun,
前面是北海岸
I'd say that's the north shore over there.
太阳在那边  那里应该是西海岸
Sun's over there. that's gotta be the west coast.
-真的吗  难道你有指南针吗  -没有  你有吗
- Really? what, you got a compass? -No. do you?
谢谢
Thank you.
在潜水艇里
For backing me up at the sub.
这没什么
No problem.
我压根不知道我们这是到了哪里
I got no idea where the hell we are.
Vincent  过来
Vincent! come here! hey!
你好吗  孩子
How you doing, boy?
那些带火的弓箭出现后我就没见过你
Since the flaming arrows three years ago. hi!
你好吗  他怎么会独自存活了下来
How you doing? how did he survive alone out here?
不
Oh, hell, no.
Bernard
Bernard!
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
那是个炸弹吗
Is that a bomb?!
别动  我得帮你止血
Try not to move. I need to stop the bleeding.
-发生什么事了  Sayid还好吗  -他很好
- What's going on back there?Is Sayid okay?- Yes,he looks ok.
你只管注意前面的路吧
Just keep your eyes on the damn road!
-我要不要停车  -停车
- Should I pull over? yeah, - Let's pull over
然后等着枪林弹雨  你就管开车吧
and get shot. Just drive.
我不知道我们的目的地是哪里
I don't know where we're going.
天鹅站  去天鹅站
The swan site.　Head the swan.
你为什么想去那里  Sayid要是枪击  何不去
Why do you want to go there? if Sayid's shot, shouldn't we...
Hurley  如果你还想救Sayid
Hurley, if you want to save Sayid,
-就带我们去天鹅站  -那好吧
- Take us to the swan．- If you want it is.
Jack  天鹅站有什么  我找到办法
Jack, what's at the swan? I think I found
可以让你回到你妻子身边
a way to get you back to your wife.
你们一直自己找吃的东西
So y'all been scavenging food
住在小屋里
And living out in a hut by yourselves.
人们一直都想
people try the whole life
为自己在海边找到一个宁静
To get themselves a nice, quiet place near the ocean
的归属  我们找到了
Where they can live in peace. and we did it.
这就是我们的家
That's what we made for ourselves.
我不是想泼你冷水
Well, i hate to rain on your parade, but...
不过  你的高级公寓马上就会毁了
Your condo's about to go ka-blooey.
Jack有个炸弹
Jack has a bomb.
管他呢
Who cares?
什么
Excuse me?
你们一直都会有这事那事
It's always something with you people.
你现在说Jack有个炸弹
Now you say jack's got a bomb.
你们想去阻止他  对吗
And what, you guys are all gonna try to stop him, right?
是的  没错
Yeah, that's right.
我们回到了30年前
We traveled back 30 years in time,
可你们还是要枪茅以对
And you're still trying to find ways to shoot each other?
Rose  我们只要知道
Rose, we just need to know
达摩的设施从这里怎么去
Which way the dharma barracks are from here
就可以阻止Jack了
So we can stop jack,
要么就只有等死
Or you're gonna be dead.
所有的人都会死
We all will.
那就死好了
So we die.
我们只关心能不能在一起
We just care about being together.
这对我们是最重要的
That's all that matters in the end.
设施在那边的5英里以外
The barracks are 5 miles that way.
Bernard  Sawyer
Bernard. Sawyer.
Rose
Rose.
我们出发吧  再见
Let's go. bye.
真的不喝杯茶吗
You sure don't want some tea?
下次吧
Maybe another time.
但愿你永远也不要让我看那盒子的东西
I wish you'd never showed me what was in this damn box.
你到底要用它干什么
What the hell you gonna do with it anyway?
我们要把它拿给一个人看
We need to show it to somebody.
为什么
What for?
这样他们就知道面临什么了
So they'll know what they're up against.
他们到底面临什么了
What exactly are they up against?
比箱子里的东西
something a hell
更可怕  Frank
Than what's in this box, frank.
不过别担心  只要跟我们在一起  你就没事
Don't worry, though. as long as you're with us, you're fine.
如果我知道你们是谁的话  我会更确信你是"朋友"
That's be reassuring if i knew who you were, "friend."
我们是好人
We are the good guys.
通常状况下  当一个人告诉你
In my experience, the people who go out of their way
他是好人  那他一定是坏人
To tell you that the good guys are the bad guys.
我们到了
We're here.
快看那些灰
Look at the ash!
感觉怎么样
你渴吗
有人来看你
我向他解释你的病情
可他还是坚持要见你
没人来探望过你  这会对你有帮助
抱歉我无法早点来
很高兴见到你
我在这是因为我需要你帮忙
I'm here because I need your help.
你能帮我吗
Can you do that?
能帮帮我吗  Ilana
Will you help me, ilana?
好的
Yes.
他不在这 他好长时间没在这里了
He isn't there, hasn't been in a long time.
有其他人来过
Someone else has been using it.
烧了它
Burn it!
我不是环保主义者
I'm no tree hugger or anything,
不过把房子烧了可能会引起森林大火
But that's a pretty good way to torch the whole jungle,
你觉得呢
Don't you think?
我想我们知道该去哪了
Well, i guess we know where we're going.
这是我们原先的营地
This is our old camp.
可爱的家
Home sweet home.
好的  大家  Richard告诉我
All right, everyone, richard tells me
必须在傍晚前到达目的地
We should get to where we're going by nightfall.
那我们干嘛不趁机
So why don't you all take this opportunity
休息一下  喘口气呢
To rest up and catch your breath?
考虑到我的计划
Considering what i have planned
大家有必要休息一下
for ya, you're gonna need it.
我在享受一个人的时光
I was enjoying some alone time.
看到你身后的东西了吗
You see what's behind you?
是一个门  怎么了
It's a door. how about that?
那不只是一个门  Ben
It's not just a door, ben.
那是我们第一次见面时  那个船舱的门
It's the door to the hatch where you and i first met.
介意我问你一个问题吗
You mind if i ask you a question?
我是双鱼座的
I'm a pisces.
那天在船舱里发生什么了
What happened that day at the cabin,
就是你第一次带我去见Jacob那天
When you first took me to meet jacob?
你可能已经知道了
Well, you clearly already know
我当时对着一张空椅子说话  John
That i was talking to an empty chair, john...
那是我假装的
That i was pretending.
当那些东西在屋子里飞舞的时候
Which is not to say that i wasn't as surprised as you were
我跟你一样惊讶
When things started flying around in the room.
但是为什么你一去
But why would you go to all the trouble
就发生了这些
To make something like that up?
我很尴尬
I was embarrassed.
我并不想让你知道我从没见过Jacob
I didn't want you to know that i had never seen jacob.
没错  我撒谎了
So, yes, i lied.
这就是我做的
That's what i do.
好的
All right, then.
那你为什么让我杀了Jacob  John
Why do you want me to kill jacob, john?
因为
Because...
尽管你一直是岛上的忠实仆人
Despite your loyal service to this island,
可是你得了癌症
You got cancer...
你不得不看着你的女儿
You had to watch your own daughter gunned down
在你的面前倒下
Right in front of you.
这就是你的这些牺牲所给你的报酬吗
And your reward for those sacrifices?
你被驱逐了
You were banished.
你以一个你从没见过的人
And you did all this
的名义做了所有这些事
In the name of a man you'd never even met.
Ben  所以问题应该是
So the question is, ben,
为什么你不想杀了Jacob
Why the hell wouldn't you wanna kill jacob?
从我们相见的那一天开始
我就爱上了你
我将用我的一生
去爱你
以此为证
我的写在纸上了
我们将永不分离
因为我们如果分开
就好像天空离开了大地
以此戒为证
你们打算什么时候要小孩
可能等我们度蜜月的时候
祝福你们
你们的爱是一件特别的事情
不要忽视它
那是谁
不知道  不过他的韩语好
还有多久
How much further?
还要5分钟
Uh, we're about five minutes away.
你无法止住血
You can't stop the bleeding.
给我干净的绷带
I need fresh dressings.
Jack  这个炸弹会怎么样
Jack, so this bomb is supposed
我们不回去
We're not going back in time.
对  因为根本不可能
Right, because that would be ridiculous.
我需要改装一下炸弹
I need to modify the bomb.
我可以让它受到冲击就爆炸
I can rig it so it detonates on impact.
Jack  我们一定要在事情发生的那一刻赶到
Jack, we need to be there at the moment of the incident.
否则一切都功亏一篑
Or all of this will be for nothing.
怎么停下了
Why the hell are we stopping?
看
That's why.